Imogen Cunningham
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Printed Material, 1903-1991, Series 8:; (boxes 5-7; 1.2 linear feet)
  - Exhibition announcements and catalogs for Cunningham, 1982-1991, (2 folders) (Box 6 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Exhibition announcements and catalogs for others, 1941-1990, (4 folders) (Box 6 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Press releases, 1955-1978, (2 folders) (Box 6 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Calendars of events, 1965-1985, (3 folders) (Box 6 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Programs, 1954-1989, (2 folders) (Box 6 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Brochures for Guggenheim fellowships, 1967-1970 (Box 6 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Brochures for art museums and galleries, undated, 1973-1976 (Box 6 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Brochures for art museums and galleries, undated, 1973-1976 (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Brochures for schools and workshops, undated, 1931-1973, (5 folders) (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Brochures for publications, concerning Cunningham, undated, 1973-1979 (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Brochures for publications, concerning others, undated, 1978 (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Brochures concerning individuals, undated, 1970 (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
    (Alice Eastwood and S. Groswold Morley)
  - Brochures for University of California at Berkeley Libraries, 1965-1985 (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Miscellaneous brochures, undated (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Reproductions of art work, undated (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Miscellaneous printed material, 1903-1967 (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
- Photographs, 1916-1976, Series 9:; (12 folders)
  The photographs in this series are of Cunningham, family members, friends, residences, gallery openings and installations, and art work by others. Four unstable silver printing out images of an unidentified elderly woman have not been microfilmed. For records relating to photographs of friends, see also Series 2: Correspondence (Dresden, Maud) for 2 postcard photographs of Dresden with Cunningham and with Omer Foisie dated May 31, 1910.
  - Photographs of Imogen Cunningham (4), 1916-1976 (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Photographs of family members, Padraic, Marjorie, and Kayla Partridge (16), 1951-1952 (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Photographs of miscellaneous family members (5), undated and 1965 (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Photographs of residences (32), circa 1946 (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Photographs of miscellaneous friends (15), 1925-1968 (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Photographs of unidentified children, undated (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Photographs of the gallery opening at Mount Angel Abbey (22), 1971, (2 folders) (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Photographs of miscellaneous gallery installations (58), 1969-1970 (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Photographs of award ceremonies (5), 1973 (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
  - Photographs of art works by others (3), undated (Box 7 (hol), Reel 5041)
- Oversized Material1947-1948, 1967, undated, Series 10:
  - 5 Imogen Cunningham Garden Plats, 1947-1948, undated (Box 8 (ov), Reel unfilmed)
  - Concert Poster, undated (Box 8 (ov), Reel unfilmed)
  - 1967 Wall Calendar signed by Cunningham, 1967 (Box 8 (ov), Reel unfilmed)